<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>Is a line of handheld electronic games produced by Nintendo from 1980 to 1991. Created by game designer Gunpei Yokoi, each Game & Watch features a single game to be played on an LCD screen in addition to a clock.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="PT">
			<text>É uma linha de consoles portáteis produzida pela Nintendo entre 1980 e 1991, criado pelo designer Gunpei Yokoi. Foi a segunda linha de aparelhos de jogos eletrônicos da Nintendo (a primeira foi o Color TV Game).</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>Is a line of handheld electronic games produced by Nintendo from 1980 to 1991. Created by game designer Gunpei Yokoi, each Game & Watch features a single game to be played on an LCD screen in addition to a clock.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>Es una línea de 59 consolas portátiles de videojuegos fabricadas por Nintendo y creadas por Gunpei Yokoi de 1980 a 1991. Cada una de ellas poseía un único juego con pantalla LCD, y tenía además reloj y alarma.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Game and Watch sont des jeux électroniques de poche produits par la société Nintendo de 1980 à 1991, ils font également office de montres et de réveils. Vendus à 43,4 millions d'exemplaires à travers le monde.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Ist eine Reihe elektronischer Handheld-Spiele, die von Nintendo von 1980 bis 1991 hergestellt wurden. Jedes Game & Watch wurde vom Spieledesigner Gunpei Yokoi entwickelt und bietet neben einer Uhr ein einzelnes Spiel, das auf einem LCD-Bildschirm gespielt werden kann.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Game & Watch</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>1980</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Nintendo</text>
		</text>
	</view>
	
		<customView name="HCoinSpin">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/gameandwatch.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


	<customView name="CoinOps Details">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/gameandwatch.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>	
	
</theme>
