<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>The series has had a significant impact on the development of console role-playing games, and introduced a number of features to the genre. Installments of the series have appeared on various computers, consoles, handheld devices, and mobile phones.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="PT">
			<text>Dragon Quest (ou Dragon Warrior como conhecido nos EUA) teve um impacto significativo no desenvolvimento de jogos de RPG de console e introduziu vários recursos ao gênero. Jogos da série apareceram em vários computadores, consoles, dispositivos portáteis e telefones celulares.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>Is a Japanese science fantasy media franchise created by Hironobu Sakaguchi, and developed and owned by Square Enix (formerly Square). The franchise centers on a series of fantasy and science fantasy role-playing video games.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>La serie ha tenido un impacto significativo en el desarrollo de los juegos de rol de consola e introdujo una serie de características en el género. Las entregas de la serie han aparecido en varias computadoras, consolas, dispositivos portátiles y teléfonos móviles.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>La série a eu un impact significatif sur le développement des jeux de rôle sur console et a introduit un certain nombre de fonctionnalités dans le genre. Des épisodes de la série sont apparus sur divers ordinateurs, consoles, appareils portables et téléphones mobiles.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Die Serie hatte einen erheblichen Einfluss auf die Entwicklung von Konsolen-Rollenspielen und führte eine Reihe von Funktionen in das Genre ein. Teile der Serie sind auf verschiedenen Computern, Konsolen, Handheld-Geräten und Mobiltelefonen erschienen.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Dragon Quest</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>1986</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Yuji Horii</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info5" extra="true">
			<text>DEVELOPER:</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info5" extra="true"  lang="PT">
			<text>DESENVOLVEDOR:</text>
		</text>
						<text name="info5" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>DEVELOPER:</text>
		</text>
						<text name="info5" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>DESARROLLADOR:</text>
		</text>
						<text name="info5" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>DÉVELOPPEUR:</text>
		</text>
		<text name="info5" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>ENTWICKLER:</text>
		</text>
	</view>

		<customView name="HCoinSpin">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


	<customView name="CoinOps Details">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>

</theme>
