<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>The SAM Coupé is an 8-bit British home computer that was first released in late 1989. It was designed to have compatibility with and is commonly considered a clone of the Sinclair ZX Spectrum computer.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="PT">
			<text>SAM Coupé é um computador doméstico britânico de 8 bits que foi lançado pela primeira vez no final de 1989. Ele foi projetado para ter compatibilidade e é comumente considerado um clone do computador Sinclair ZX Spectrum.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>The SAM Coupé is an 8-bit British home computer that was first released in late 1989. It was designed to have compatibility with and is commonly considered a clone of the Sinclair ZX Spectrum computer.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>El SAM Coupé es una computadora doméstica británica de 8 bits, lanzada por primera vez a fines de 1989. Fue diseñada para ser compatible con y generalmente se considera un clon de la computadora Sinclair ZX Spectrum.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Le SAM Coupé est un ordinateur domestique britannique 8 bits, lancé pour la première fois à la fin de 1989. Il a été conçu pour être compatible avec et est généralement considéré comme un clone de l'ordinateur Sinclair ZX Spectrum.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>Das SAM Coupé ist ein britischer 8-Bit-Heimcomputer, der erstmals Ende 1989 auf den Markt kam. Es wurde entwickelt, um mit dem Sinclair ZX Spectrum-Computer kompatibel zu sein, und wird allgemein als Klon des Sinclair ZX Spectrum-Computers angesehen.</text>
		</text>


		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>SAM Coupe</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>1989</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Miles Gordon Technology</text>
		</text>
	</view>

		<customView name="HCoinSpin">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/coinopstv.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


	<customView name="CoinOps Details">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/coinopstv.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>
</theme>
