<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>Is a platform game developed by Core Design originally for the Acorn Archimedes, Amiga, Atari ST, Amstrad CPC, ZX Spectrum, Commodore 64, and MS-DOS. The game was released in 1989 and published by MicroProse on the Firebird Software label in the UK, and on the MicroPlay label in America. </text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true"  lang="PT">
			<text>É um jogo de plataforma desenvolvido pela Core Design originalmente para Acorn Archimedes, Amiga, Atari ST, Amstrad CPC, ZX Spectrum, Commodore 64 e MS-DOS. O jogo foi lançado em 1989 e publicado pela MicroProse no selo Firebird Software no Reino Unido e no selo MicroPlay na América.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>Is a platform game developed by Core Design originally for the Acorn Archimedes, Amiga, Atari ST, Amstrad CPC, ZX Spectrum, Commodore 64, and MS-DOS. The game was released in 1989 and published by MicroProse on the Firebird Software label in the UK, and on the MicroPlay label in America. </text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>Es un juego de plataformas desarrollado por Core Design originalmente para Acorn Archimedes, Amiga, Atari ST, Amstrad CPC, ZX Spectrum, Commodore 64 y MS-DOS. El juego fue lanzado en 1989 y publicado por MicroProse en el sello Firebird Software en el Reino Unido y en el sello MicroPlay en Estados Unidos.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Est un jeu de plateforme développé par Core Design à l'origine pour Acorn Archimedes, Amiga, Atari ST, Amstrad CPC, ZX Spectrum, Commodore 64 et MS-DOS. Le jeu est sorti en 1989 et publié par MicroProse sur le label Firebird Software au Royaume-Uni et sur le label MicroPlay en Amérique.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Ist ein Plattformspiel, das von Core Design ursprünglich für Acorn Archimedes, Amiga, Atari ST, Amstrad CPC, ZX Spectrum, Commodore 64 und MS-DOS entwickelt wurde. Das Spiel wurde 1989 veröffentlicht und von MicroProse auf dem Label Firebird Software in Großbritannien und auf dem Label MicroPlay in Amerika veröffentlicht.</text>
		</text>

		
		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Rick Dangerous</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>1989</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Core Design</text>
		</text>			
	</view>
	
		<customView name="HCoinSpin">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


	<customView name="CoinOps Details">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>
	
</theme>