<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>The Philips P2000T home computer was Philips' first real entry in the home computer market in 1980, after the Philips Videopac G7000 game system (better known in North America as the Magnavox Odyssey2) which they already sold to compete with the Atari 2600 and similar game systems. There was also a P2000M version with an additional 80-column text card for use with a monochrome monitor. This version shipped with a monitor cabinet also housing a dual 5¼-inch floppy disk drive. The P2000C version, introduced in 1982, was portable.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="PT">
			<text>O computador doméstico Philips P2000T foi a primeira entrada real da Philips no mercado de computadores domésticos em 1980, após o sistema de jogos Philips Videopac G7000 (mais conhecido na América do Norte como Magnavox Odyssey2), que já era vendido para competir com o Atari 2600 e sistemas de jogos semelhantes. Havia também uma versão P2000M com uma placa de texto adicional de 80 colunas para uso com um monitor monocromático. Essa versão era fornecida com um gabinete de monitor que também abrigava uma unidade de disquete dupla de 5¼ polegadas. A versão P2000C, lançada em 1982, era portátil.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>The Philips P2000T home computer was Philips' first real entry in the home computer market in 1980, after the Philips Videopac G7000 game system (better known in North America as the Magnavox Odyssey2) which they already sold to compete with the Atari 2600 and similar game systems. There was also a P2000M version with an additional 80-column text card for use with a monochrome monitor. This version shipped with a monitor cabinet also housing a dual 5¼-inch floppy disk drive. The P2000C version, introduced in 1982, was portable.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>El ordenador doméstico Philips P2000T fue la primera incursión real de Philips en el mercado de los ordenadores domésticos en 1980, tras la consola Philips Videopac G7000 (más conocida en Norteamérica como Magnavox Odyssey2), que ya comercializaban para competir con la Atari 2600 y otras consolas similares. También existía una versión P2000M con una tarjeta de texto adicional de 80 columnas para su uso con un monitor monocromo. Esta versión se comercializó con una carcasa de monitor que también albergaba una unidad de disquete doble de 5¼ pulgadas. La versión P2000C, presentada en 1982, era portátil.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>L'ordinateur domestique Philips P2000T a été la première véritable incursion de Philips sur le marché des ordinateurs domestiques en 1980, après la console de jeux Philips Videopac G7000 (mieux connue en Amérique du Nord sous le nom de Magnavox Odyssey2) qu'ils commercialisaient déjà pour concurrencer l'Atari 2600 et d'autres consoles similaires. Il existait également une version P2000M avec une carte texte supplémentaire de 80 colonnes à utiliser avec un moniteur monochrome. Cette version était livrée avec un boîtier de moniteur contenant également un double lecteur de disquettes 5¼ pouces. La version P2000C, lancée en 1982, était portable.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Der Philips P2000T Heimcomputer war 1980 Philips' erster richtiger Einstieg in den Heimcomputermarkt, nachdem das Unternehmen bereits das Philips Videopac G7000 Spielsystem (in Nordamerika besser bekannt als Magnavox Odyssey2) verkauft hatte, um mit dem Atari 2600 und ähnlichen Spielsystemen zu konkurrieren. Es gab auch eine P2000M-Version mit einer zusätzlichen 80-Spalten-Textkarte für die Verwendung mit einem Monochrom-Monitor. Diese Version wurde mit einem Monitorgehäuse ausgeliefert, in dem auch ein doppeltes 5¼-Zoll-Diskettenlaufwerk untergebracht war. Die 1982 eingeführte P2000C-Version war tragbar.</text>
		</text>
    
    <text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ZH">
			<text></text>
		</text>
    
    <text name="info1" extra="true" lang="TW">
			<text></text>
		</text>

		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Philips P2000T</text>
		</text>
    
		<text name="info2" extra="true" lang="ZH">
			<text></text>
		</text>

    
		<text name="info2" extra="true" lang="TW">
			<text></text>
		</text>

		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>1980</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Philips</text>
		</text>        
    
    <text name="info4" extra="true" lang="ZH">
			<text></text>
		</text>
    
    <text name="info4" extra="true" lang="TW">
			<text></text>
		</text>

	</view>
</theme>