<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>Is the last generation of MSX computers that was put to market by a household electronic brand. Only Panasonic was brave enough to put faith in the standard once again, by releasing two different models. MSX Turbo R computers were produced until 1994.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="PT">
			<text>É a última geração de computadores MSX que foi colocada no mercado por uma marca de eletrônicos domésticos. Apenas a Panasonic foi corajosa o suficiente para colocar fé no padrão mais uma vez, lançando dois modelos diferentes. Os computadores MSX Turbo R foram produzidos até 1994.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>Is the last generation of MSX computers that was put to market by a household electronic brand. Only Panasonic was brave enough to put faith in the standard once again, by releasing two different models. MSX Turbo R computers were produced until 1994.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>Es la última generación de ordenadores MSX lanzada al mercado por una marca de electrónica doméstica. Solo Panasonic fue lo suficientemente valiente como para volver a confiar en el estándar y lanzó dos modelos diferentes. Las computadoras MSX Turbo R se produjeron hasta 1994.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Est la dernière génération d'ordinateurs MSX qui a été mise sur le marché par une marque d'électronique domestique. Seul Panasonic a eu le courage de faire à nouveau confiance à la norme, en lançant deux modèles différents. Les ordinateurs MSX Turbo R ont été produits jusqu'en 1994.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Ist die letzte Generation von MSX-Computern, die von einer Haushaltselektronikmarke auf den Markt gebracht wurde. Nur Panasonic war mutig genug, wieder auf den Standard zu setzen und zwei verschiedene Modelle herauszubringen. MSX Turbo R Computer wurden bis 1994 produziert.</text>
		</text>


		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>MSX Turbo R</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>1990</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>ASCII</text>
		</text>
	</view>

	<customView name="HCoinSpin">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/msx.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


	<customView name="CoinOps Details">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/msx.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


</theme>
