<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>Are very small, portable devices for playing interactive electronic games, often miniaturized versions of video games. The controls, display and speakers are all part of a single unit.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="PT">
			<text>São dispositivos portáteis muito pequenos para jogar jogos eletrônicos interativos, muitas vezes versões miniaturizadas de videogames. Os controles, a tela e os alto-falantes fazem parte de uma única unidade.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>Are very small, portable devices for playing interactive electronic games, often miniaturized versions of video games. The controls, display and speakers are all part of a single unit. </text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>Son dispositivos portátiles muy pequeños para jugar juegos electrónicos interactivos, a menudo versiones miniaturizadas de videojuegos. Los controles, la pantalla y los altavoces forman parte de una sola unidad.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Sont de très petits appareils portables pour jouer à des jeux électroniques interactifs, souvent des versions miniaturisées de jeux vidéo. Les commandes, l'affichage et les haut-parleurs font tous partie d'une seule unité.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Sind sehr kleine, tragbare Geräte zum Spielen interaktiver elektronischer Spiele, oft miniaturisierte Versionen von Videospielen. Bedienelemente, Display und Lautsprecher sind alle Teil einer Einheit.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>LCD Games</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>19XX</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Various</text>
		</text>
	</view>
	
	
	<customView name="HCoinSpin">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/gameandwatch.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


	<customView name="CoinOps Details">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/gameandwatch.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>	
</theme>
