<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>The VTech Laser 310 is an 8-bit home computer from the Hong Kong computer company VTech (Video Technology Limited) from the 1980s. It was sold in England, France, Spain and Australia as the Dick Smith VZ-300.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true"  lang="PT">
			<text>O VTech Laser 310 é um computador doméstico de 8 bits da empresa de computadores de Hong Kong VTech (Video Technology Limited) da década de 1980. Foi vendido na Inglaterra, França, Espanha e Austrália como Dick Smith VZ-300.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>The VTech Laser 310 is an 8-bit home computer from the Hong Kong computer company VTech (Video Technology Limited) from the 1980s. It was sold in England, France, Spain and Australia as the Dick Smith VZ-300.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>El VTech Laser 310 es un ordenador doméstico de 8 bits de la empresa informática de Hong Kong VTech (Video Technology Limited) de la década de 1980. Se vendió en Inglaterra, Francia, España y Australia como Dick Smith VZ-300.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Le VTech Laser 310 est un ordinateur domestique 8 bits de la société informatique de Hong Kong VTech (Video Technology Limited) des années 1980. Il a été vendu en Angleterre, en France, en Espagne et en Australie sous le nom de Dick Smith VZ-300.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Der VTech Laser 310 ist ein 8-Bit-Heimcomputer des Computerunternehmens VTech (Video Technology Limited) aus Hongkong aus den 1980er Jahren. Er wurde in England, Frankreich, Spanien und Australien als Dick Smith VZ-300 verkauft.</text>
		</text>

		
		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>VTech Laser 310</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>1983</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>VTech</text>
		</text>			
	</view>
	
		<customView name="HCoinSpin">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


	<customView name="CoinOps Details">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>
	
</theme>