<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>Android is a mobile operating system based on a modified version of the Linux kernel and other open source software, designed primarily for touchscreen mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true"  lang="PT">
			<text>Android é um sistema operacional móvel baseado em uma versão modificada do kernel Linux e outro software de código aberto, projetado principalmente para dispositivos móveis com tela sensível ao toque, como smartphones e tablets.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>Android is a mobile operating system based on a modified version of the Linux kernel and other open source software, designed primarily for touchscreen mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>Android es un sistema operativo móvil basado en una versión modificada del kernel de Linux y otro software de código abierto, diseñado principalmente para dispositivos móviles con pantalla táctil, como teléfonos inteligentes y tabletas.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Android est un système d'exploitation mobile basé sur une version modifiée du noyau Linux et d'autres logiciels open source, conçu principalement pour les appareils mobiles à écran tactile tels que les smartphones et les tablettes.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Android ist ein mobiles Betriebssystem, das auf einer modifizierten Version des Linux-Kernels und anderer Open-Source-Software basiert und hauptsächlich für Touchscreen-Mobilgeräte wie Smartphones und Tablets entwickelt wurde.</text>
		</text>

		
		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Android</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>2008</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Various (Google)</text>
		</text>			
	</view>
	
		<customView name="HCoinSpin">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


	<customView name="CoinOps Details">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>
	
</theme>