<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>It is a video game console developed by Sony Computer Entertainment. It is the successor to PlayStation 2. It was released on November 11, 2006, in Japan, November 17, 2006 in North America and on March 23, 2007 in Europe and Oceania.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="PT">
			<text>É um console de videogames desenvolvido pela Sony Computer Entertainment. É o sucessor do PlayStation 2. Foi lançado em 11 de novembro de 2006, no Japão, 17 de novembro de 2006 na América do Norte e em 23 de março de 2007 na Europa e Oceania.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>It is a video game console developed by Sony Computer Entertainment. It is the successor to PlayStation 2. It was released on November 11, 2006, in Japan, November 17, 2006 in North America and on March 23, 2007 in Europe and Oceania.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>Es una consola de videojuegos desarrollada por Sony Computer Entertainment. Es el sucesor de PlayStation 2. Fue lanzado el 11 de noviembre de 2006 en Japón, el 17 de noviembre de 2006 en América del Norte y el 23 de marzo de 2007 en Europa y Oceanía.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>C'est une console de jeu vidéo développée par Sony Computer Entertainment. Il est le successeur de PlayStation 2. Il est sorti le 11 novembre 2006 au Japon, le 17 novembre 2006 en Amérique du Nord et le 23 mars 2007 en Europe et en Océanie.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Es ist eine von Sony Computer Entertainment entwickelte Videospielkonsole. Es ist der Nachfolger von PlayStation 2. Es wurde am 11. November 2006 in Japan, am 17. November 2006 in Nordamerika und am 23. März 2007 in Europa und Ozeanien veröffentlicht.</text>
		</text>    
    
		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ZH">
			<text>它是由索尼电脑娱乐公司开发的视频游戏机。它是 PlayStation2的继任者。它于2006年11月11日在日本发布，2006 年 11 月 17 日在北美发布，2007 年 3 月 23 日在欧洲和大洋洲发布。</text>
		</text>   
    
		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="TW">
			<text>它是由索尼電腦娛樂公司開發的視頻遊戲機。它是 PlayStation2的繼任者。它於2006年11月11日在日本發布，2006 年 11 月 17 日在北美發布，2007 年 3 月 23 日在歐洲和大洋洲發布。</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Sony PlayStation 3</text>
		</text>      
    
		<text name="info2" extra="true" lang="ZH">
			<text>索尼PlayStation3</text>
		</text>
    
		<text name="info2" extra="true" lang="TW">
			<text>索尼PlayStation3</text>
		</text>   

		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>2006</text>
		</text>    

		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Sony Computer Entertainment</text>
		</text> 
    
		<text name="info4" extra="true" lang="ZH">
			<text>索尼电脑娱乐</text>
		</text> 
    
		<text name="info4" extra="true" lang="TW">
			<text>索尼電腦娛樂</text>
		</text>       
    
    
	</view>
</theme>
