<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>Atomiswave é uma placa de arcade lançada pela Sammy Corporation em 2003, baseado nas especificações técnicas do Sega Dreamcast (portanto, em termos técnicos, levemente inferior à Sega NAOMI).</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true"  lang="PTBR">
			<text>Atomiswave é uma placa de arcade lançada pela Sammy Corporation em 2003, baseado nas especificações técnicas do Sega Dreamcast (portanto, em termos técnicos, levemente inferior à Sega NAOMI).</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>Atomiswave is an arcade card released by Sammy Corporation in 2003, based on the Sega Dreamcast technical specifications (thus slightly lower than Sega NAOMI in technical terms).</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>Atomiswave es una tarjeta arcade lanzada por Sammy Corporation en 2003, basada en las especificaciones técnicas de Sega Dreamcast (muy ligeramente inferior a Sega NAOMI en términos técnicos).</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Atomiswave est une carte arcade publiée par Sammy Corporation en 2003, basée sur les spécifications techniques de Sega Dreamcast (donc légèrement inférieure à celle de Sega NAOMI sur le plan technique).</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Atomiswave ist eine Arcade-Karte, die 2003 von der Sammy Corporation herausgebracht wurde und auf den technischen Spezifikationen von Sega Dreamcast basiert (also etwas niedriger als Sega NAOMI in technischer Hinsicht).</text>
		</text>

    <text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ZH">
			<text>Atomiswave是Sammyn的定制街机系统板和机柜。它基于世嘉的Dreamcast主机，与NAOMI有相似之处，因为它使用可互换的游戏卡带，以及用于更改控制方案的可拆卸模块（包括双操纵杆、双光枪和方向盘），但不像NAOMI，与 Dreamcast 相比，Atomiswave没有扩展RAM。</text>
		</text>
    
    <text name="info1" extra="true" lang="TW">
			<text>Atomiswave是Sammy的定製街機系統板和機櫃。它基於世嘉的Dreamcast主机，與NAOMI有相似之處，因為它使用可互換的遊戲卡帶，以及用於更改控製方案的可拆卸模塊（包括雙操縱桿、雙光槍和方向盤），但不像NAOMI，與 Dreamcast 相比，Atomiswave沒有擴展RAM。</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Atomiswave</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>2003</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Sammy Corporation</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
