<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>Is a Japanese variant of PC, built by Fujitsu from February 1989 to the summer of 1997. It started as a proprietary PC variant intended for multimedia applications and games, but later became more compatible with IBM PC compatibles.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true"  lang="PT">
			<text>É uma variante japonesa do PC, construída pela Fujitsu de fevereiro de 1989 ao verão de 1997. Começou como uma variante de PC proprietária destinada a aplicativos de multimídia e jogos de PC.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>Is a Japanese variant of PC, built by Fujitsu from February 1989 to the summer of 1997. It started as a proprietary PC variant intended for multimedia applications and games, but later became more compatible with IBM PC compatibles.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>Es una variante japonesa de PC, construida por Fujitsu desde febrero de 1989 hasta el verano de 1997. Comenzó como una variante de PC patentada destinada a aplicaciones multimedia y juegos de PC.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Il s'agit d'une variante japonaise du PC, construite par Fujitsu de février 1989 à l'été 1997. Elle a commencé comme une variante PC propriétaire destinée aux applications multimédias et aux jeux PC.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Ist eine japanische PC-Variante, die von Fujitsu von Februar 1989 bis Sommer 1997 gebaut wurde. Sie begann als proprietäre PC-Variante für Multimedia-Anwendungen und Spiele, wurde aber später besser mit IBM-PC-kompatiblen Geräten kompatibel.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>FM Towns</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>1989</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Fujitsu</text>
		</text>
	</view>

	<customView name="HCoinSpin">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/coinpc.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


	<customView name="CoinOps Details">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/coinpc.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>

</theme>
