<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>The Dragon 32 was a home computer produced in the 1980s. The Dragon 32 was very similar to Tandy's TRS-80 Color Computer (CoCo) and was created especially for the European market by Mettoy/Dragon Data Ltd., based in Port Talbot. , Wales.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true"  lang="PT">
			<text>O Dragon 32 foi um computador doméstico produzido na década de 1980. O Dragon 32 era muito similar ao TRS-80 Color Computer (CoCo) da Tandy e foi criado especialmente para o mercado europeu pela Mettoy/Dragon Data Ltda., estabelecida em Port Talbot, País de Gales.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>The Dragon 32 was a home computer produced in the 1980s. The Dragon 32 was very similar to Tandy's TRS-80 Color Computer (CoCo) and was created especially for the European market by Mettoy/Dragon Data Ltd., based in Port Talbot. , Wales.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>El Dragon 32 fue un ordenador doméstico producido en la década de 1980. El Dragon 32 era muy similar al TRS-80 Color Computer (CoCo) de Tandy y fue creado especialmente para el mercado europeo por Mettoy/Dragon Data Ltd., con sede en Port Talbot. , Gales.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Le Dragon 32 était un ordinateur domestique produit dans les années 1980. Le Dragon 32 était très similaire à l'ordinateur couleur TRS-80 (CoCo) de Tandy et a été créé spécialement pour le marché européen par Mettoy/Dragon Data Ltd., basé à Port Talbot. Pays de Galles.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Der Dragon 32 war ein in den 1980er Jahren hergestellter Heimcomputer, der dem TRS-80 Color Computer (CoCo) von Tandy sehr ähnlich war und speziell für den europäischen Markt von Mettoy/Dragon Data Ltd. mit Sitz in Port Talbot entwickelt wurde. Wales.</text>
		</text>

		
		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Dragon 32</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>1982</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Dragon Data</text>
		</text>			
	</view>
	
		<customView name="HCoinSpin">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


	<customView name="CoinOps Details">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>
	
</theme>