<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>Neo Geo é uma família da hardware de videogames desenvolvido pela SNK. A marca originou-se com a liberação de um sistema arcade, o Neo Geo MVS e sua contraparte de console doméstico, o Neo Geo AES.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="PTBR">
			<text>Neo Geo é uma família da hardware de videogames desenvolvido pela SNK. A marca originou-se com a liberação de um sistema arcade, o Neo Geo MVS e sua contraparte de console doméstico, o Neo Geo AES.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>Neo Geo is a family of video game hardware developed by SNK. On the market from 1990 to 2004, the brand originated with the release of an arcade system, the MVS and its home console counterpart, the Neo Geo AES.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>Neo-Geo es el nombre de un sistema de 16 bits basado en cartuchos para arcades así como videoconsolas para el hogar lanzado en 1990 por la compañía de videojuegos japonesa SNK.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Neo-Geo est un système de jeux vidéo pour borne d'arcade compatible JAMMA destiné aux salles d'arcade et créé par la société japonaise SNK en 1990.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Neo Geo ist eine Familie von Videospielhardware, die von SNK entwickelt wurde. Die Marke, die von 1990 bis 2004 auf dem Markt war, entstand mit der Veröffentlichung eines Arcade-Systems, dem MVS, und seinem Gegenstück für die Heimkonsole, dem Neo Geo AES.</text>
		</text>      
    
    <text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ZH">
			<text>Neo Geo 是由 SNK 开发的视频游戏硬件系列。从 1990 年到 2004 年在市场上，该品牌起源于街机系统 Neo Geo MVS 及其家用游戏机 Neo Geo AES 的发布。</text>
		</text>
    
    <text name="info1" extra="true" lang="TW">
			<text>Neo Geo 是由 SNK 開發的視頻遊戲硬件系列。從 1990 年到 2004 年在市場上，該品牌起源於街機系統 Neo Geo MVS 及其家用遊戲機 Neo Geo AES 的發布。</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Neo Geo</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>1990</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>SNK Corporation</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
