<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>O APF Microcomputer System é um console de videogame doméstico baseado em cartucho de 8 bits de segunda geração lançado pela APF Electronics Inc. com seis cartuchos. O console é frequentemente referido como M-1000 ou MP-1000.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true"  lang="PTBR">
			<text>O APF Microcomputer System é um console de videogame doméstico baseado em cartucho de 8 bits de segunda geração lançado pela APF Electronics Inc. com seis cartuchos. O console é frequentemente referido como M-1000 ou MP-1000.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>APF Microcomputer System is a second generation 8-bit cartridge-based home video game console released in October 1978 by APF Electronics Inc. with six cartridges. The console is often referred to M-1000 or MP-1000.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>APF Microcomputer System es una consola de videojuegos doméstica basada en cartuchos de 8 bits de segunda generación lanzada por APF Electronics Inc. con seis cartuchos. La consola a menudo se denomina M-1000 o MP-1000.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>APF Microcomputer System est une console de jeu vidéo domestique à cartouche 8 bits de deuxième génération lancée par APF Electronics Inc. avec six cartouches. La console est souvent appelée M-1000 ou MP-1000.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Das APF-Mikrocomputersystem ist eine 8-Bit-Heimvideospielkonsole der zweiten Generation, die im Oktober 1978 von APF Electronics Inc. mit sechs Kassetten veröffentlicht wurde. Die Konsole wird oft als M-1000 oder MP-1000 bezeichnet.</text>
		</text>

		
		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>APF-MP1000</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>1978</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>APF Electronics Inc</text>
		</text>			
	</view>
	
		<customView name="HCoinSpin">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


	<customView name="CoinOps Details">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>
	
</theme>