<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>Is a home video game console released by Nintendo on November 19, 2006. As a seventh-generation console, the Wii competed with Microsoft's Xbox 360 and Sony's PlayStation 3.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="PT">
			<text>É um console de videogame doméstico produzido pela Nintendo e lançado em 2006. É um videogame da sétima geração e o quinto console da Nintendo. Seus principais concorrentes são o Xbox 360 e o Playstation 3.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>Is a home video game console released by Nintendo on November 19, 2006. As a seventh-generation console, the Wii competed with Microsoft's Xbox 360 and Sony's PlayStation 3.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>Wii (ウィー Uī) es una videoconsola producida por Nintendo y estrenada el 19 de noviembre de 2006 en Norteamérica y el 8 de diciembre del mismo año en Europa. Perteneciente a la séptima generación de consolas.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Wii (ウィー, Wī) est une console de jeux de salon du fabricant japonais Nintendo, sortie en 2006. Console de la septième génération, tout comme la Xbox 360 et la PlayStation 3 avec lesquelles elle est en rivalité.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Ist eine Heimvideospielkonsole, die am 19. November 2006 von Nintendo herausgebracht wurde. Als Konsole der siebten Generation konkurrierte die Wii mit Microsofts Xbox 360 und Sonys PlayStation 3.</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ZH">
			<text>任天堂于2006年11月19日发布的一款家用视频游戏机。作为第七代游戏机，Wii与微软的Xbox360和索尼的PlayStation3竞争。</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="TW">
			<text>任天堂於2006年11月19日發布的家用電玩遊戲機。作為第七代遊戲機，Wii與微軟的Xbox360和索尼的PlayStation3競爭。</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Nintendo Wii</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info2" extra="true" lang="ZH">
			<text>任天堂Wii</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info2" extra="true" lang="TW">
			<text>任天堂Wii</text>
		</text>
				<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>2006</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Nintendo</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>