<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>Konami é um conglomerado japonês de entretenimento e jogos de azar. Opera como distribuidor de produtos (que produz e distribui anime, tokusatsu, caça-níqueis,e máquinas de pachinko), desenvolvedor de videogame e empresa editora.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="PTBR">
			<text>Konami é um conglomerado japonês de entretenimento e jogos de azar. Opera como distribuidor de produtos (que produz e distribui anime, tokusatsu, caça-níqueis,e máquinas de pachinko), desenvolvedor de videogame e empresa editora.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>Konami is a Japanese entertainment and gambling conglomerate. It operates as a product distributor (which produces and distributes trading cards, anime, tokusatsu, slot machines, pachinko machines and arcade cabinets), video game developer and publisher company.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>Konami es un conglomerado japonés de entretenimiento y juegos de azar. Funciona como un distribuidor de productos (que produce y distribuye anime, tokusatsu, máquinas tragamonedas y máquinas pachinko), desarrollador de videojuegos y compañía editorial.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Konami est un conglomérat de divertissement et de jeu japonais. Il opère en tant que distributeur de produits (qui produit et distribue des animés, des tokusatsu, des machines à sous et des armoires d'arcade), développeur de jeux vidéo et société d'édition.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Konami ist ein japanisches Unterhaltungs- und Glücksspielkonglomerat. Es ist als Produktvertreiber (der Sammelkarten, Anime, Tokusatsu, Spielautomaten, Pachinko-Automaten und Arcade-Schränke produziert und vertreibt), Entwickler von Videospielen und Verlagsunternehmen tätig.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Konami</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>1973</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Kagemasa Kozuki</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info5" extra="true">
			<text>FUNDADOR:</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info5" extra="true"  lang="PTBR">
			<text>FUNDADOR:</text>
		</text>
		<text name="info5" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>FOUNDER:</text>
		</text>
		<text name="info5" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>FUNDADOR:</text>
		</text>
		<text name="info5" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>FONDATEUR:</text>
		</text>
		<text name="info5" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>GRÜNDER:</text>
		</text>
	</view>

		<customView name="HCoinSpin">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


	<customView name="CoinOps Details">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>
</theme>
