<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>Is an American video game publisher based in New York City. The company was established in December 1998 as a subsidiary of Take-Two Interactive, using the assets Take-Two had previously acquired from BMG Interactive.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true"  lang="PT">
			<text>É uma publisher e desenvolvedora americana de videogames com sede na cidade de Nova York. A empresa foi fundada em dezembro de 1998 como subsidiária da Take-Two Interactive, usando os ativos que a Take-Two havia adquirido anteriormente da BMG Interactive.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>Is an American video game publisher based in New York City. The company was established in December 1998 as a subsidiary of Take-Two Interactive, using the assets Take-Two had previously acquired from BMG Interactive.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>Es un editor de videojuegos estadounidense con sede en la ciudad de Nueva York. La compañía se estableció en diciembre de 1998 como una subsidiaria de Take-Two Interactive, utilizando los activos que Take-Two había adquirido previamente de BMG Interactive.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Est un éditeur américain de jeux vidéo basé à New York. La société a été créée en décembre 1998 en tant que filiale de Take-Two Interactive, en utilisant les actifs que Take-Two avait précédemment acquis de BMG Interactive.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Ist ein amerikanischer Herausgeber von Videospielen mit Sitz in New York City. Das Unternehmen wurde im Dezember 1998 als Tochtergesellschaft von Take-Two Interactive gegründet und nutzte die Vermögenswerte, die Take-Two zuvor von BMG Interactive erworben hatte.</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Rockstar Games</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>1998</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Sam Houser</text>
		</text>	

				<text name="info5" extra="true">
			<text>FOUNDER:</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info5" extra="true"  lang="PT">
			<text>FUNDADOR:</text>
		</text>
						<text name="info5" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>FOUNDER:</text>
		</text>
						<text name="info5" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>FUNDADOR:</text>
		</text>
						<text name="info5" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>FONDATEUR:</text>
		</text>
		<text name="info5" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>GRÜNDER:</text>
		</text>	
		
	</view>
	
		<customView name="HCoinSpin">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


	<customView name="CoinOps Details">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>
	
</theme>