<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>The main games in the series follow the events of the King of Iron Fist Tournament, hosted by the Mishima Zaibatsu, where players control a plethora of characters to win the tournament; the conflict between the Mishima family serves as the main focus of the series' plot.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="PT">
			<text>Os jogos principais da série seguem os eventos do Torneio King of Iron Fist, organizado pela Mishima Zaibatsu, onde os jogadores controlam uma infinidade de personagens para vencer o torneio; o conflito entre a família Mishima serve como o foco principal do enredo da série.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>The main games in the series follow the events of the King of Iron Fist Tournament, hosted by the Mishima Zaibatsu, where players control a plethora of characters to win the tournament; the conflict between the Mishima family serves as the main focus of the series' plot.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>Los juegos principales de la serie siguen los eventos del Torneo King of Iron Fist, organizado por Mishima Zaibatsu, donde los jugadores controlan una plétora de personajes para ganar el torneo; el conflicto entre la familia Mishima sirve como el foco principal de la trama de la serie.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Les principaux jeux de la série suivent les événements du King of Iron Fist Tournament, organisé par le Mishima Zaibatsu, où les joueurs contrôlent une pléthore de personnages pour gagner le tournoi; le conflit entre la famille Mishima est au centre de l'intrigue de la série.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Die Hauptspiele der Serie folgen den Ereignissen des King of Iron Fist-Turniers, das von Mishima Zaibatsu veranstaltet wird, wo die Spieler eine Fülle von Charakteren steuern, um das Turnier zu gewinnen; Der Konflikt zwischen der Familie Mishima dient als Hauptfokus der Handlung der Serie.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Tekken</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>1994</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Seiichi Ishii</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info5" extra="true">
			<text>CREATED BY:</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info5" extra="true"  lang="PT">
			<text>CRIADO POR:</text>
		</text>
						<text name="info5" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>CREATED BY:</text>
		</text>
						<text name="info5" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>CRIADO POR:</text>
		</text>
						<text name="info5" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>CRÉÉ PAR:</text>
		</text>
		<text name="info5" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>ERSTELLT VON:</text>
		</text>
	</view>

	<customView name="HCoinSpin">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


	<customView name="CoinOps Details">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>
</theme>
