<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>Aqui você poderá editar configurações do sistema, alterar opções de cores e emuladores, além de ter acesso a scripts de diversas funcionalidades. Para sair de alguma opção, saia como um jogo normal.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true"  region="PTBR">
			<text>Here you will be able to edit system settings, change color options and emulators, in addition to having access to scripts of various functionalities. To get out of any option, leave as a normal game.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" region="EN">
			<text>RetroBat is a set of Batch and Powershell scripts written to easily configure and launch EmulationStation for Windows. This frontend software is intended to gather your ROMs collection and run games with compatible emulators such as RetroArch.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" region="ES">
			<text>Aquí podrá editar la configuración del sistema, cambiar las opciones de color y los emuladores, además de tener acceso a los scripts de varias funcionalidades. Para salir de cualquier opción, déjalo como un juego normal.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" region="FR">
			<text>Ici, vous pourrez modifier les paramètres du système, changer les options de couleur et les émulateurs, en plus d'avoir accès à des scripts de diverses fonctionnalités. Pour sortir de toute option, partez comme un jeu normal.</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Setup</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>20XX</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Various</text>
		</text>	

		<text name="info5" extra="true">
			<text>DESENVOLVEDOR:</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info5" extra="true"  region="PTBR">
			<text>DESENVOLVEDOR:</text>
		</text>
						<text name="info5" extra="true" region="EN">
			<text>DEVELOPER:</text>
		</text>
						<text name="info5" extra="true" region="ES">
			<text>DESARROLLADOR:</text>
		</text>
						<text name="info5" extra="true" region="FR">
			<text>DÉVELOPPEUR:</text>
		</text>			
	</view>
</theme>
