<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>Commodore 16 é um computador doméstico fabricado pela Commodore International com uma CPU 7501 ou 8501 compatível com 6502, lançada em 1984 e destinada a ser um computador básico para substituir o VIC-20. Teve algum sucesso na Europa.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="PTBR">
			<text>Commodore 16 é um computador doméstico fabricado pela Commodore International com uma CPU 7501 ou 8501 compatível com 6502, lançada em 1984 e destinada a ser um computador básico para substituir o VIC-20. Teve algum sucesso na Europa.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>Commodore 16 is a home computer made by Commodore International with a 6502-compatible 7501 or 8501 CPU, released in 1984 and intended to be an entry-level computer to replace the VIC-20. It enjoyed some success in certain European countries.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>Commodore 16 es una computadora doméstica hecha por Commodore International con una CPU 7501 u 8501 compatible con 6502, lanzada en 1984 y destinada a ser una computadora de nivel de entrada para reemplazar el VIC-20. Gozó de cierto éxito en Europa.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Commodore 16 est un ordinateur domestique fabriqué par Commodore International avec un processeur 7501 ou 8501 compatible 6502, sorti en 1984 et destiné à être un ordinateur d'entrée de gamme pour remplacer le VIC-20. Il connaît un certain succès en Europe.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Commodore 16 ist ein von Commodore International hergestellter Heimcomputer mit einer 6502-kompatiblen 7501- oder 8501-CPU, der 1984 herausgebracht wurde und als Einstiegscomputer den VIC-20 ersetzen soll. In bestimmten europäischen Ländern war es einigermaßen erfolgreich.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Commodore 16</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>1984</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Commodore Business Machines</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
