<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>Jazz Jackrabbit game port: series of games developed by Epic Megagames exclusively for PC and a GBA version. Jazz, a green hare who wields the "LFG-2000" plasma gun, crosses surreal landscapes to save her planet Carrotus and Princess Eva.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true"  lang="PT">
			<text>Port do jogo Jazz Jackrabbit, série de jogos desenvolvidos pela Epic Megagames exclusivos para computador e uma versão de GBA. Jazz, uma lebre verde que porta a arma de plasma "LFG-2000", atravessa cenários surreais para salvar seu planeta Carrotus e a Princesa Eva.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>Jazz Jackrabbit game port: series of games developed by Epic Megagames exclusively for PC and a GBA version. Jazz, a green hare who wields the "LFG-2000" plasma gun, crosses surreal landscapes to save her planet Carrotus and Princess Eva.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>Puerto de juego Jazz Jackrabbit: serie de juegos desarrollados por Epic Megagames exclusivamente para PC y una versión GBA. Jazz, una liebre verde que empuña la pistola de plasma "LFG-2000", atraviesa paisajes surrealistas para salvar a su planeta Carrotus y a la Princesa Eva.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Port de jeu Jazz Jackrabbit : série de jeux développés par Epic Megagames exclusivement pour PC et une version GBA. Jazz, un lièvre vert qui manie le pistolet à plasma "LFG-2000", traverse des paysages surréalistes pour sauver sa planète Carrotus et la princesse Eva.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Jazz Jackrabbit Gameport: Reihe von Spielen, die von Epic Megagames exklusiv für PC und eine GBA-Version entwickelt wurden. Jazz, ein grüner Hase, der die Plasmakanone „LFG-2000“ führt, durchquert surreale Landschaften, um ihren Planeten Carrotus und Prinzessin Eva zu retten.</text>
		</text>

		
		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>OpenJazz</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>2005</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Alister Thomson</text>
		</text>			
	</view>
	
		<customView name="HCoinSpin">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


	<customView name="CoinOps Details">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>
	
</theme>