<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>Arcade is an electronic gaming device installed in entertainment establishments. It consists of an enclosure, CRT or monitor, power supply, game controller (s) and game system.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="PT">
			<text>Arcade é um aparelho de jogo eletrônico instalado em estabelecimentos de entretenimento. Compõe-se de um gabinete, tubo de imagem (CRT) ou monitor, fonte de alimentação, controle(s) de jogo e sistema de jogo.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>Arcade is an electronic gaming device installed in entertainment establishments. It consists of an enclosure, CRT or monitor, power supply, game controller (s) and game system.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>Arcade es un dispositivo de juego electrónico instalado en establecimientos de entretenimiento. Consiste en un gabinete, CRT o monitor, fuente de alimentación, controlador (es) de juego y sistema de juego.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Arcade est un appareil de jeu électronique installé dans les établissements de divertissement. Il comprend un boîtier, un tube cathodique ou un moniteur, une alimentation, des contrôleurs de jeu et un système de jeu.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Arcade ist ein elektronisches Spielgerät, das in Unterhaltungseinrichtungen installiert ist. Es besteht aus Gehäuse, CRT oder Monitor, Netzteil, Gamecontroller(n) und Spielsystem.</text>
		</text>    
    
    <text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ZH">
			<text>街机是安装在公共娱乐场所的电子游戏设备。它由外壳、CRT或显示器、电源、游戏控制器和游戏系统组成。</text>
		</text>
    
    <text name="info1" extra="true" lang="TW">
			<text>街機是安裝在公共娛樂場所的電子遊戲設備。它由外殼、CRT或顯示器、電源、遊戲控制器和遊戲系統組成。</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Arcade</text>
		</text> 
    
		<text name="info2" extra="true" lang="ZH">
			<text>街机</text>
		</text>
    
		<text name="info2" extra="true" lang="TW">
			<text>街機</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>19XX</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Various</text>
		</text>
    
		<text name="info4" extra="true" lang="ZH">
			<text>各厂商</text>
		</text>
    
		<text name="info4" extra="true" lang="TW">
			<text>各廠商</text>
		</text>    
    
	</view>

	<customView name="HCoinSpin">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/cps1.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


	<customView name="CoinOps Details">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/cps1.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>
</theme>
