<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>ST-V (Sega Titan Video) is an arcade system board released by Sega in 1994. Departing from their usual process of building custom arcade hardware, Sega's ST-V is essentially identical to the Sega Saturn home console system.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true"  lang="PT">
			<text>ST-V (Sega Titan Video) é uma placa de sistema de arcade lançada pela Sega em 1994. Partindo de seu processo usual de construção de hardware de arcade personalizado, o ST-V da Sega é essencialmente idêntico ao sistema de console doméstico Sega Saturn.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>ST-V (Sega Titan Video) is an arcade system board released by Sega in 1994. Departing from their usual process of building custom arcade hardware, Sega's ST-V is essentially identical to the Sega Saturn home console system.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>ST-V (Sega Titan Video) es una placa de sistema arcade lanzada por Sega en 1994. Partiendo de su proceso habitual de creación de hardware arcade personalizado, la ST-V de Sega es esencialmente idéntica al sistema de consola doméstica Sega Saturn.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>ST-V (Sega Titan Video) est une carte système d'arcade publiée par Sega en 1994. S'écartant de leur processus habituel de construction de matériel d'arcade personnalisé, le ST-V de Sega est essentiellement identique au système de console de salon Sega Saturn.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>ST-V (Sega Titan Video) ist eine Arcade-Systemplatine, die 1994 von Sega herausgebracht wurde. Segas ST-V ist im Wesentlichen identisch mit dem Sega Saturn-Heimkonsolensystem und weicht vom üblichen Prozess des Baus benutzerdefinierter Arcade-Hardware ab.</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Sega Titan Video</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>1994</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Sega</text>
		</text>			
	</view>
	
		<customView name="HCoinSpin">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


	<customView name="CoinOps Details">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>
	
</theme>