<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>Xbox is a home video game console and the first installment in the Xbox series of video game consoles manufactured by Microsoft. It is classified as a sixth generation console, competing with PS2 and GameCube.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="PT">
			<text>O Xbox é um console de videogame doméstico e o primeiro da série fabricados pela Microsoft. É classificado como um console de sexta geração, competindo com o PlayStation 2 da Sony e o GameCube da Nintendo.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>Xbox is a home video game console and the first installment in the Xbox series of video game consoles manufactured by Microsoft. It is classified as a sixth generation console, competing with PS2 and GameCube.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>Xbox es una consola de videojuegos doméstica y la primera de la serie fabricada por Microsoft. Está clasificada como una consola de sexta generación, compitiendo con PlayStation 2 de Sony y GameCube de Nintendo.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>La Xbox est une console de jeux vidéo de salon et le premier opus de la série de consoles de jeux vidéo Xbox fabriquées par Microsoft. Elle est classée parmi les consoles de sixième génération, en concurrence avec la PS2 et la GameCube.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Xbox ist eine Videospielkonsole für den Heimgebrauch und die erste Folge der Xbox-Reihe von Videospielkonsolen, die von Microsoft hergestellt werden. Sie wird als Konsole der sechsten Generation eingestuft und konkurriert mit PS2 und GameCube.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ZH">
			<text>Xbox是一款家用视频游戏机，是微软生产的Xbox系列视频游戏机的第一款。它被归类为第六代游戏机，与PS2和GameCube竞争。</text>
		</text>   

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="TW">
			<text>Xbox是一款家用視頻遊戲機，是微軟生產的Xbox系列視頻遊戲機的第一款。它被歸類為第六代遊戲機，與PS2和GameCube競爭。</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Microsoft Xbox</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info2" extra="true" lang="ZH">
			<text>微软Xbox</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info2" extra="true" lang="TW">
			<text>微軟Xbox</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>2001</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Microsoft</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="info4" extra="true" lang="ZH">
			<text>微软</text>
		</text> 

		<text name="info4" extra="true" lang="TW">
			<text>微軟</text>
		</text> 		
	</view>

</theme>
